Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonder.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We'll live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary lives.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Bumble, sir, look, it's the Straw Hat!
That was close!
I'm really sick of you
guys, you know that?
What's your problem?
You were getting it our way even
before we got to this island.
Huh?
Not these guys again.
Last time I ran into you, I couldn't
fight, because I had to protect my friends.
But now...
Oh, you guys are so gonna get it!
How dare you?
Do you know who you attacked?
This is no lowly commoner.
This is Wapol, the king and
absolute ruler of Drum Kingdom.
That's right.
Show some respect.
He's this country's monarch.
How dare you do such a thing to his
most excellent of excellencies for shame
So I take it you've run afoul
of Wapol before young man.
I sure have he's that annoying
big mouth pirate What'd he do?
He ate part of our ship and
then he attacked me and my
friends This guy's got it coming
and I'm gonna give it to him.
Okay, but before you do that
aren't you cold in that get up?
You know cold Hey, did
he say he was a king?
But I thought he was a pirate!
Took you long enough! Ha!
So you're disrespectful
and have wax in your ears!
But yeah, Wapol is the king
of Drum Kingdom, Straw Hat!
Oh, it's freezing out here!
You really are an idiot!
Yeah, it's 50 below zero!
I think they're ignoring us!
Wait, sir!
Straw Hat, you've got
some nerve. Just wait.
I'm going to bite you into pieces!
I'm sorry, but you'll have
to hang on for just a minute.
He had to go get a coat
Tell me
Your friend he can
stretch himself. Oh, huh?
Oh that it's because he's a rubber man
What the heck is that?
It's a monster.
Well, well, looks like we're
up against that old hag.
A reindeer and a few of the Straw Hats.
Not that much of a challenge?
This will be over quickly, and
once we've eliminated them,
there won't be anyone else
foolhardy enough to defy me!
Of course, my king.
Today will be remembered as the day you
restored Drum Kingdom to its former glory.
I'll start with you, Dr.
Kureha.
You've committed a major offense
by moving into my castle,
and even a greater one by
flying that strange flag!
It's not yours!
Not anymore, Terra looks grave.
I wasn't interested in this rundown place,
what with all the bad things you did here.
But we could use it to
do some good and the
reindeer insisted on
flying the doctor's flag.
Doctor he fought to save this country by
raising that flag how dare you desecrate my
castle by flying the flag of that stupid
doctor i command that it
be burned immediately.
I'll never let you touch that
flag or get inside this castle.
Never.
Look, sir, he's that.
You're right, it is him.
He's that doctor's monster,
the one Dalton stopped.
That flag there, it's
a symbol of his faith.
I won't let you take it
down, not now, not ever.
We're going to take it
and all of you down.
And we're going into the castle.
Show them no mercy, boys.
Old lady, are you gonna fight, too?
Old lady?
If they're more than you can
handle, Junior, I'll step in.
Appreciate that.
Don't you worry, sir.
We'll get them out of your hair.
And speaking of hair!
Dr. Reed!
Hey, big man with the afro,
didn't your mother ever tell you
it's not right to strike a lady?
Especially not a hot young one.
Now that's more like it, blondie.
What's that? Huh?
Damn, why won't this
stupid thing come off?
What's making it stick to me?
Static electricity or something?
Exactamundo.
Damn it, get off my leg,
you disgusting hairball!
Cold!
I need a coat really quick.
Any coat will do.
What's going on outside?
I heard a lot of noise.
It's freezing out there.
Have you seen any coats around?
I didn't ask that.
What I want to know is
what's happening out there.
It's just a fight. Oh.
Do you guys need help?
Nah, stay in bed.
If you need a coat, you can borrow mine.
What?
But it's a girl's coat and it's ugly.
Well, you did say any coat will do.
Oh, yeah.
Well, as long as it keeps me warm.
Huh.
I wonder what all the fuss was about.
I swear I'm gonna smack
that hair of all guys silly
whenever I finally get
this nasty thing off me!
Oh, well, in that case...
Monomo static-cleave!
Gross!
Raydeer!
Help me!
Kenny!
Get these things off me!
Please!
No!
No! No!
What's wrong with you?
You keep them!
Will you two please
stop goofing around? Ha!
There's a reason I don't
keep my hair conditioned.
And a very good one at that, too.
Their dryness makes them
burst into flames much easier.
Oh, no!
He's gonna burn these things!
Here! Huh?
Hey, what are you doing?
Decoy plan!
Decoy plan?
Wait, I'm the decoy? Check it, mate!
Oh, no!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Oh, no! Chopper!
This might be a girl's
coat, but it's really warm.
Luffy, grab my leg from there! Leg? Sure!
Like this?
Yep, just don't let go!
Oh, gotcha!
Armaged in a air assault!
Can't you help me!
Go on, shoot!
Not too shabby.
Thanks, you two.
You guys are so amazing.
Hey, wait, just a minute.
Isn't that Nami's coat
you're wearing, Luffy?
Whoa, Big Mouth's still alive, but
his hippo's headed to the moon.
Take it off right now, jerk.
Wapples, sir, are you all right?
We've underestimated them.
They're stronger than we thought.
Then it's time to bring out my
big guns and my bigger appetite.
I'll show them the true
power of the much-much fruit.
Very good, sir.
That's right!
I'll show them the Much Much Factory!
Oh, he stood up!
Yeah, but how?
You hit him pretty hard.
Guess he's tough?
You can't die! Dalton, please!
Don't worry.
He's not dead.
The 20 MDs!
He will be if we don't act soon.
He has severe frostbite.
We can begin treating him
immediately if you'll let us.
Hey what do you know there
are doctors here that's funny
i thought i heard there
weren't any sawbones in this
country there are a few doctors
these guys are the 20 mds
but they work exclusively for
wobble so that makes them bad
doctors that's right we can't
trust any of you traitors you
expect us to leave dalton with
you you surrendered to waffle
without a fight and turned your
backs on us wobble probably
sent you here to kill dalton
please if you want to save
him just do as I say.
The 20 of us are still doctors,
even though we were forced against
our wills to serve only Wapol.
We've always worked to advance
our medical research for
the benefit of all the
patients in this country.
It was all because of a certain quack who
taught us never to give up.
We can't afford to lose any more men
like him, so please let Let us hope.
Hey, Chess, tell me what I ate today
and in the exact order that I ate it.
Well, sir, you started by
eating two cannons on the ship,
one sauteed in butter and the other raw.
Then it was a cannonball
and gunpowder salad
followed by the main course
of a toasted cottage.
And you thought I ate a lot.
You do, but this guy's
a bigger pig than you.
You see, Straw Hats?
Whatever I eat becomes part of my
body thanks to the munch-munch fruit.
What's happening?
What the...
Munch Munch shot!
The Wumple House!
A house?
Now, if you'll please
excuse me, I have to eat!
Behold the Munch Munch Factory!
No way!
He's eating his own men!
That's so mean!
Feast your eyes on this!
Come forth, you miraculous union!
What kind of union?
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am the strongest
warrior of Drum Kingdom.
Desmarmo!
Ha!
Miraculous Union?
More like Ridiculous Union.
Sweet!
It's ridiculous!
Just don't let your guard down.
They might look silly,
but don't be fooled.
They're tough.
So tough that the citizens
couldn't stand against them.
That's how these thugs were
able to exile all the doctors.
Article one of the Drum
Kingdom's constitution.
Those who don't do as the king
wishes will be put to death.
That's the number one law of this country.
You refused my wishes and broke that law.
Now you are all going to be
punished for your crimes.
But first I'm going to
deal with the matter
of that quacks flag
sullying my regal castle.
It's time I took that thing down!
A pirate flag.
Hey, reindeer, that flag.
Nothing is impossible for a
man who raises the pirate flag.
Isn't that what I told you, huh?
How dare you!
You attacked Doctor's flag, you freak!
Doctor tried to...
He tried to save even you!
Chopper, try not to hold a
grudge against us humans, okay?
This country is sick right now.
The people and the king both suffer
from a terrible sickness of the heart.
But this is Walpole, Doctor.
Someone as bad as him
isn't worth saving, is he?
Huh?
I...
I won't hurt you if you just
leave this country forever!
Chopper, what are you doing?!
Even if he does promise that, you
can't trust a word that desperate says!
But...
Doctor said...
Chopper!
Hey, Big Mouth! Huh?
Straw Hat!
You guys weren't real pirates, you
were just fake ones, weren't you?
That's why you don't know what
flying a pirate flag means!
Cause you were just a bunch of
fakes who didn't risk your lives!
That guy...
I can't take this anymore.
Let's go up the mountain, okay, Usopp? Mr.
Bushido, this sitting around
and waiting is killing me.
Luffy and the others could have
gotten hurt in that avalanche.
They might be trapped.
And don't forget, Nami had a high fever.
Anything's happened to them.
You're worried about
Nami and Luffy and Sanji
and Dalton and what's
going on in Alabasta.
Vivi, can't you see it?
You're carrying too many
burdens on your shoulders.
Calm down.
We don't need to go up there at all.
And do you know why?
Because those three are fine,
and that's Luffy and Nami and
Sand you were talking about.
I believe in them.
It's right. It's right.
You have to have faith in your friends.
Musop does, and that's
why he can be so calm.
I get it now.
Thanks a lot.
You're full of wisdom, Musop.
No, he's full of crap.
He's just afraid to go up that mountain.
Gah!
But I heard that there were things like
yetis and huge man-eating buddies up there!
I don't want to get eaten!
Then say so from the start, coward.
Okay, I don't want to be some monster
snack, and I'm sure they're fine.
Luffy can work out anything.
Dalton, no. Wait!
Hey, it's Dalton. Thank goodness.
Would somebody please
tell me who this guy is?
Dalton, listen to reason.
Get out of my way.
We can't let Wobbly retake the castle.
We just can't.
Wait, you mean that's where
you're heading, the castle?
In your condition?
Are you nuts?
My country is far more
important than my health.
He cannot succeed.
I will not let that happen.
Not now, not ever.
Wapol must perish.
But you're not strong enough to
fight them in your condition, sir.
Then the rest of us are
no match for them either.
I'm going to settle this
thing once and for all.
I'll stop Wapol even if it kills me.
Here, I'll take you to the castle.
Hop on.
Come on now, don't be so modest.
I just want you to save your
strength for the fight, that's all.
Consider it.
Just hold tight.
Okay, here it goes.
We'll be there in no time.
Usopp meant well.
Um, Usopp, thanks, but,
uh, this isn't working.
Just give me a second, OK?
I haven't quite hit my stride yet.
Besides, I told you I was going to
get you to the castle and I will.
Now that I caught my breath here,
we can get back under very weight.
Damn it, what the hell is he doing?
You're just going to sit there and
whine, or are you coming with us?
Zoro!
You stupid jerk!
You thunder stealer!
Shut up, I'm trying to put your...
Knock it off!
Why did you do that?
Just as I was getting my
second win, too. I was!
Sure you were.
I was!
I'll tell you what to shoot.
I'm going to kick your...
Hey, wait, hold up.
There's an easier way up to the castle.
Huh?
Instead of walking, take the
ropeway. Ropeway? Impossible.
There hasn't been one connecting
to Waple's castle for a while.
Someone's obviously reconnected
one because I just saw it.
There was a rope leading
from the castle to
a big white tree on the
outskirts of Gyasta. Gyasta, huh?
That's the name of the town that Dr.
Kureha was headed to, remember?
What a pirate flag!
Mean Straw Hat!
Don't make me laugh.
Flags have no meaning.
If you think that, you're
dumber than you look.
What?
Listen, pirate flags stand
for something, Big Mouth.
They're not raised to some kind of joke.
Moron, the only joke is that I've
let you live as long as I have.
Since you dared put that flag
back after I knocked it down,
it's time I delivered the punchline.
Take your best shot, Big Mouth.
You can't break this flag.
The skull on it is a symbol of fate.
Hey, you! Look out!
Luffy!
That was her direction!
He and that flag were blown to pieces!
Told you see how do you do
that it's impossible I have
no idea who this pirate flag
originally Belonged to but it
doesn't matter a pirate flag is
someone's pledge to risk their
life It's not something to be
shot at or made fun of jerks
It stands for something
that you stupid jackasses
will never understand
not in a million years?
Incredible!
So this...
is a pirate!
What are pirates?
They're dashing swashbucklers.
It's great to be a pirate.
The most amazing people sail the seas.
Chopper, someday you've got to go.
Hey reindeer! Huh?
I'm gonna kick these guys butts for
showing your friends' flag disrespect!
You in?
Uh, me?
You idiot!
You just don't get it, do you?
All right, then, since you feel
so strongly about that flag,
I'll destroy you along with it!
I don't think so, tubby.
Looks like your backbone gave out.
Your condition will continue
to worsen if you keep moving.
So stop!
Rocker's order!
If you two want to fight amongst yourselves,
then please, by all means, do so.
But I hope you'll at least watch your
friend and that flag get blown to bits.
Straw Hat, say your prayers!
Stop it!
That's the spirit!
Go get him, reindeer guy!
Cape, sir, watch out!
Would you look at that?
The little furball's got more
courage than a full-grown man.
Ha, ha, ha!
I'm sorry, Frank, but there's no way I'm
gonna let you lay a single paw on our king.
Wow, there really are some
strange creatures in this world.
You must be that Yeti the
villagers hated and feared.
They tried to kill you and
chased you away, right?
I bet you spent your whole
life all alone with no friends.
You're a monster.
Nobody likes you.
People want to kill you.
But here you are trying
to save this country.
That's the stupidest thing I ever heard!
Shut up!
Even if I don't have friends, I can
still buy for something I believe in!
And as long as the flag
flies, I will! Hey!
That's not true!
Huh?
YOU DO HAVE FRIENDS!
I'M YOUR FRIEND, RAIN, AND ME!
Oh, no! Straw Hat!
You should be flat as a pancake!
Yeah, but I'm fine,
because I'm a rubber man.
Rubber?
hey reindeer can you finish off
that two-headed guy for me that one
over there piece of cake good while
you're doing that i'll take care
of this one you dare to knock me
this country's monarch over you'll
pay for that insult i'm taking you
down is that so you and what army
Huh, you little freak?
Freak?
That's like the pot
calling the kettle black.
If you keep moving around,
you may lose the ability to walk,
so just stay down there and shut up.
And don't worry.
When push comes to shove, my
little reindeer can hold his own.
Listen up!
My name's Tony Tony Chopper, not Freak!
It's a name the world's
greatest doctor gave me!
He was a wonderful man.
Even if he forgave you for disrespecting
his flag, I won't forgive you!
The only one who will
show no forgiveness is me.
I'll stomp you.
Rumbleball.
My life has been too still.
My heart is unfulfilled.
Like you could be the one to set me free.
Something has to change.
My world can be arranged.
I'll do anything as
long as you are with me.
I've grown stronger having you by my side.
We've started on an everlasting ride.
I'm invincible when your love is near.
When I'm with you I have no fear.
Let's see how far we can make this go.
The world is ours.
You're just right, I know.
I see it shine in the distance,
glistening like water when
the sun rises in the dawn.